Consider the same example as earlier,
在之前的例子中
where we asked if the mean height for all coffee drinkers was greater than 70 inches.
我们问喝咖啡的所有人的平均身高是否大于 70 英寸 (1.78 米)
We could again set up a null and alternative hypotheses like these.
我们可以建立这样的零假设和对立假设
A second approach that is commonly done for making
在假设检验中做决策的
decisions in hypothesis testing is the following,
第二种常用方法如下
we assume that the null is true and we know what the sampling distribution would look
假如零假设为真 如果我们用零假设里最接近对立假设的值进行模拟
like if we were to simulate from the closest value under the null to the alternative.
我们可以知道抽样分布的形状
That is, this value of 70.
这个值是 70
That's the closest value under this hypothesis to our alternative hypothesis.
这是零假设里最接近对立假设的值
We could use the standard deviation of the sampling distribution to determine what
我们可以用抽样分布的标准偏差确定
the sampling distribution would look like if it came from the null hypothesis.
如果这个值来自零假设 抽样分布是什么形状
We'll simulate from a normal distribution in this case.
在这个例子中 我们对正态分布进行模拟
I'm going to pull over the code that we used before to
我将复制之前使用的代码
get the standard deviation of our sampling distribution.
以便获得我们的抽样分布的标准偏差
So the standard deviation of our sampling distribution is equal to 0.2658.
抽样分布的标准偏差等于 0.2658
And we know that if it came from
我们知道 如果它来自
this null hypothesized value of 70 what it would look like.
70 的零假设值 它会是什么形状
By the central limit theorem,
根据中心极限定理
we know that it would follow a normal distribution.
我们知道 它服从正态分布
Now, from the NumPy documentation on normal distributions,
现在 从 NumPy 的正态分布文档中
we see we can simulate draws from the normal using the hypothesized mean at
我们了解了可以用以下方法 用 70 的假设均值和抽样分布的标准偏差
70 and the standard deviation of our sampling distribution in the following way.
对正态分布中的抽取值进行模拟
So here, the loc tells us that the mean of 70 will go in this value,
这里 “loc” 表示均值 也就是 70
and the scale is the standard deviation that we want to use.
“scale” 是我们想要使用的标准偏差
So that's the standard deviation of our sampling distribution.
是我们的抽样分布的标准偏差
And we can simulate, say,
我们可以模拟其中的
10,000 values from that.
1 万个值
Each of the simulated draws here represents a possible mean from the null hypothesis.
这里的每个被模拟抽取值代表零假设中的一个可能均值
We can now ask the question of where the sample mean falls in this distribution.
我们现在可以问一个问题 样本均值位于这个分布中的哪个位置
If we go back and look at what our sample mean was,
回顾一下样本均值
we can see that it falls far below this distribution from the norm.
可以看出 它远远低于这个正态分布
If our sample mean were to fall closer to the center value of 70,
如果样本均值接近 70 的中心值
it would be a value that we would expect from the null hypothesis and therefore,
它就是零假设中的值 因此
we think the null is more likely to be true.
我们认为零假设更可能为真
In this case, with our sample means so far out in the tail,
现在这种情况下 样本均值位于尾部之外
it's far enough that we don't think it probably came from this null hypothesized value.
我们不太可能认为它来自这个零假设值